[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What will happen very soon if the cat is washing its face according to Russian beliefs?", "correct_answer": "Guests will come.", "incorrect_answers": ["It is going to rain.", "Somebody will die.", "Someone will get pregnant."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2008 film is a remake of the Spanish horror film REC.", "correct_answer": "Quarantine", "incorrect_answers": ["When a Stranger Calls", "Dawn of the Dead", "Friday the 13th"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Named after the leading sylph in Alexander Popes poem Rape of the Lock, the moon Ariel is the natural satellite of which planet of the solar system?", "correct_answer": "Uranus", "incorrect_answers": ["Jupiter", "Neptune", "Saturn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For which of these global tendencies in nature are fungi responsible?", "correct_answer": "Decline of amphibian populations", "incorrect_answers": ["Water poisoning", "Decline of tree populations", "Global warming"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who received the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Actor for 1996?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Pauly Shore for Bio-Dome", "Tom Arnold for Big Bully", "Tom Arnold for Carpool"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not among the vacuoles functions in the cell?", "correct_answer": "Production of ATP", "incorrect_answers": ["Exporting unwanted substances", "Capturing food materials", "Maintaining the internal pH"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How is the traditional Jamaican bread called Bammy prepared?", "correct_answer": "By frying", "incorrect_answers": ["By boiling", "By roasting on a spit", "By baking"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of animal is the smallest known reptile on the planet?", "correct_answer": "Gecko", "incorrect_answers": ["Lizard", "Snake", "Turtle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first successful experiment with nuclear fission, the process in which the nucleus of an atom splits into two or more smaller nuclei, was conducted in which year?", "correct_answer": "1938", "incorrect_answers": ["1932", "1934", "1936"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie Rat Race was inspired by Its a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World and had the same basic plot. What year did Rat Race come out?", "correct_answer": "2001", "incorrect_answers": ["1999", "2000", "2002"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A fungus of the Armillaria ostoyae genus, discovered in the Malheur National Forest in the Strawberry Mountains of eastern Oregon, U.S. is often cited as which of these?", "correct_answer": "The largest living organism", "incorrect_answers": ["The oldest living organism", "The fastest-growing living organism", "The smallest living organism"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Clouds are made up of these.", "correct_answer": "Water droplets and ice crystals", "incorrect_answers": ["Carbon atoms", "Oxygen ions", "Dust mites"]}]